WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
My body movements
have finally returned...
Blood...
Tsunade-sama!
Hey! Hey! What's happening?!
Why's Kabuto-san fighting
with Granny Tsunade?!
Take a good look at the headband!
He's Orochimaru's subordinate.
Eat It!
Rasengan of Anger
That man is Orochimaru...
Shizune, you take care of
the guy with the glasses...
I'll take care of Orochimaru.
Before that, I'd like to have Tsunade
do something about this body.
The effects of that drug
might still last for awhile...
There's nothing that
I can do about it.
What? Really?
Jeez. I guess it can't be helped.
I have no choice
but to fight in this condition.
Tsunade... Rest your body
with Recovery Ninjutsu.
Then... What about me, me?
You guard Tsunade together
with that pig.
What?! I want to fight, too.
Even I can...
No, you won't!
Like that four-eyed kid said, right?
You're on a different level.
The opponent is a Sannin like myself,
and the man who killed
the Third Hokage.
An eye for an eye...
I'm the only one who can fight him.
And that four-eyed guy possesses
the same level of power as Kakashi.
Okay.
Then... Shadow Clo...
Hold it!
Don't use the Shadow Clone Jutsu.
It'd be utterly pointless.
What?
It wouldn't even become
much of a diversion...
It'd be a waste of Chakra...
with them as opponents.
Now then, let's get this thing started.
— Summoning Jutsu.
Hi.
— Huh?!
— What is this?!
— Wha...?!
— What the hell's going on?!
Long time no see.
On account of the drug,
Jiraiya-sama still can't build up
Chakra very well.
It looks like your stupid
still hasn't healed, eh, Jiraiya.
That's too much even for you
with no ability.
It seems Tsunade got you
with something.
A sacrifice was necessary for that Jutsu,
so perhaps she was thinking ahead
and drugged him
with something that
would contain his power.
To think she'd make
a sacrifice of Jiraiya...
Well, it sounds just like Tsunade.
To think I'd already have
my handicap spotted.
You are such
a disgraceful guy as always...
Damn it. It kind of ticks me off
when the Pervy Sage is mocked.
Summoning... Jutsu!
The Nine-Tailed Fox kid
from the Chunin Exam.
I wonder if I should've killed him then,
after all.
For the sake of the Akatsuki organization,
I acknowledged his achievement...
and let him slide by.
But the only ones who can break
a Five-Pronged Spell
are the Sannin members
and the Third Hokage.
Which means Jiraiya-sama may have
already taught it to Naruto-kun.
Perhaps.
If he's able to control
the Nine-Tailed Fox's power...
Oh...
Th-This is...
It doesn't quite look to be so.
He isn't endowed with Shinobi ability
to begin with, so...
Why?
He's still got a long way to go,
sure enough.
Why?!
Hello.
Hey, Gamatatsu.
Why did you come out?
Oh, Gamakichi nii-chan.
It's the first time I've been Summoned.
I-I wonder if I can do my best?
Idiot. Get some snacks
or something and hide.
What? I can get snacks?
Goody-goody.
Here I go.
I'll take Jiraiya.
I leave the rest to you.
It's unfortunate...
Here I also wanted to fight Jiraiya-sama,
one of the Sannin.
Naruto!
Your opponent is me.
Earth Style! Dark Swamp!
Damn it. I can't completely sink them
with such a puny swamp.
The drug is still working.
But... with this, the snakes can't move.
Ninja Art! Poison Fog!
I'll be up a creek if
I take even one breath.
My leg tendons...!
I won't be eaten twice...!
No way!
Here I go.
Ninja Art! Needle Jizo!
Damn it... The Jutsu isn't working well.
Even if we both have handicaps,
you won't one-up me...
Give up now.
It's unfortunate...
Here I had respected you
as a fellow Medical Ninja.
Stop. Stay back!
Please hang on, Tsunade-san...
The Sannin name, which Orochimaru-sama
is also called, will cry.
My body's heavy.
To think you who were
once called the village madness
would ferry around such a kid
and struggle tirelessly for the village.
You've really fallen, haven't you?
I have a keen eye to discern ability.
And that kid... is mediocrity in my eyes.
It's precisely for this reason...
that I don't need the Uchiha kid.
It's no fun raising a genius
who's good from the start.
So you can't leave him alone
because it's like you're looking
at your old self?
That kid can't beat Uchiha who inherited
the inherent Sharingan Shinobi skill.
And that's because Naruto-kun
doesn't possess the Sharingan.
Shinobi ability is about whether
one can use and master
all the Jutsu of the world.
Ninja refers to one
who can use Ninjutsu.
Shinobi ability is no such thing.
You still don't get it?
A Ninja... is one who endures.
It's a difference of opinion, huh.
I'll teach you one thing.
What's most important for Shinobi ability...
isn't the number of Jutsu
one possesses.
What's important is...
The mettle...
not to give up.
Enough already... you jerk!
The mettle to never give up...
He possesses that.
Heh. I don't know what Jutsu you learned,
but you can't hit me with
such a large motion.
No good.
It won't easily hit with
a moving opponent.
Ouch!
And the Chakra isn't
completely held, yet...
It seems you got a cracked thigh bone
in your left leg
from the battle with the snake.
Well, you can still move if
it's just the bone.
But it's impossible now...
The lateral vastus muscle
in your right leg is totally cut off.
What should I do...?
That Jutsu of mine uses both hands.
If even one arm is taken out, it's over.
Are you scared of me?
Do you want to run away from here?
Naruto-kun, as I recall,
you said this
during the first Chunin Exam.
Don't mess with me. I won't run away!
"Don't mess with me. I won't run away."
"I'll take it. Even if I'm a Genin for
life..."
"I'll become the Hokage at any cost,
so it's okay with me."
"I'm not scared."
Can you say the same thing
right now?
Unlike you...
I will be the heir to the Hokage name
no matter what!
— Hokage is my dream!
You're not a kid anymore,
so you shouldn't act like one.
Depending on the situation,
when you want to give up and run away,
you should run away.
Oh my... What's with that look?
You'll die! If you die,
there are no dreams or anything...
Do you want to die?
You're still a Genin,
so you should run away on the battlefield.
Don't tell a man to run away.
Kids think that everything is easy.
That's why they talk about foolish dreams
like nothing at all.
That's why they can't give up.
Jiraiya, was it you
who taught him that Rasengan?
Are you acting like a teacher by teaching
a Jutsu that can't be learned?
Don't give him false hopes.
That's why the oblivious kid starts joking
that he'll become the Hokage!
They chase after foolish dreams...
and then die.
If I have three days,
I'll master that Jutsu.
Then let's make a bet.
Bastard!
As for me... I stand by my words.
That's... my Ninja Way!
A bet?
I'll give you one week.
If you can master that Jutsu,
I'll acknowledge that
you'll be able to become the Hokage...
and give you this necklace.
You should've just
stayed out of this...
Why?
Why?!
Grannny Tsunade...
You're still going to get up?
Just like our wager
I will definitely win
that unlucky necklace from you.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Shadow Clone won't do anything now.
Enough... Don't protect me, Naruto.
Stop it!
I told you that you'd die
if you were obstinate like that, right?
If you die, there will be no dreams,
no nothing.
Just get out of the way. Run away.
Humph... It's okay.
I...
until I become Hokage...
I absolutely will not die!
This way, I can hold on to you.
Here I go!
It's the same Chakra movement
as before.
No, this is... different.
I see.
In order to gain a hand
for suppressing Chakra,
the Shadow Clone...
Compress Chakra and...
hold it completely.
Wha...?!
I-It can't be.
Rasengan!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
I never forget my ideal...
to develop the Village Hidden in the Leaf
and protect its people.
The Hokage have sacrificed
their lives for that dream.
And now,
I also will put my life on the line.
From this moment,
I am the Fifth Hokage!
Next time:
"The Fifth Hokage, a Life or Death battle!"